http://www.islandstyle.net.au/flex/privacy-policy/49/1

Bits n Pieces
Your shopping cart is empty for the moment.
Country
Please Select
AustraliaUSACanadaFranceGermanyUnited KingdomJapanAfghanistanAlbaniaAlgeriaAngolaAnguillaAntigua & BarbudaArgentinaArmeniaAscension & St. HelenaAustriaAzerbaijanBahamasBahrainBangladeshBarbadosBelarusBelgiumBelizeBeninBermudaBhutanBoliviaBosnia-HerzegovinaBotswanaBrazilBritish Indian Ocean Terr.Brunei DarussalamBulgariaBurkina FasoBurundiCambodiaCameroonCape VerdeCaroline Is.Cayman Is.Central African Rep.ChadChileChinaColombiaComorosCongoCongo Dem. Rep.Cook Is.Costa RicaCote d'IvoireCroatiaCubaCyprusCzech RepublicDenmarkDjiboutiDominicaDominican Rep.EcuadorEast TimorEgyptEl SalvadorEquatorial GuineaEritreaEstoniaEthiopiaFalkland Is. (Malvinas)Faroe Is.FijiFinlandFrench GuineaFrench PolynesiaGabonGambiaGeorgiaGhanaGibraltarGreeceGreenlandGrenadaGuadeloupeGuamGuatemalaGuineaGuinea-BissauGuyanaHaitiHawaiiHondurasHong KongHungaryIcelandIndiaIndonesiaIranIraqIrelandIsrealItalyJamaicaJordanKazakhstanKenyaKiribatiKorea (north)Korea (South)KuwaitKyrgyzstanLaosLatviaLebanonLesothoLiberiaLibyan Arab JamahiriyaLiechtensteinLithuaniaLuxemburgMacaoMacedoniaMadagascarMalawiMalaysiaMaldivesMaliMaltaMariana Is.Marshall Is.MartiniqueMauritaniaMauritiusMexicoMicronesiaMoldovaMonacoMongoliaMontserratMoroccoMozambiqueMaynmarNamibiaNauruNepalNetherlandsNetherlands Antilles & ArubaNew CaledoniaNew ZealandNicaraguaNigerNigeriaNorfolk Is.NorwayOmanPakistanPalauPanamaPapua New GuineaParaguayPeruPhilippinesPitcairn Is.PolandPortugalPuerto RicoQatarReunionRomaniaRussiaRwandaSt. Christopher & NevisSt. LuciaSt.Pierre & MiquelonSt. Vincent & the GranadinesSamoa, AmericanSamoa, WesternSao Tome & PrincinpeSaudi ArabiaSenegalSeychellesSierra LeoneSingaporeSlovakiaSloveniaSolomon Is.SomaliaSouth AfricaSpainSri LankaSudanSurinameSwazilandSwedenSwitzerlandSyriaTaiwanTajikistanTanzaniaThailandTogoTokelau Is.TongaTrindad & TobagoTristan Da CunhaTunisiaTurkeyTurkmenistanTurks & Caicos Is.TuvaluUgandaUkraineUnited Arab EmiratesUruguayUzbekistanVanuatuVatican City StateVenezuelaVietnamVirgin Is. (UK)Virgin Is. (USA)Wallis & Futuna Is.yemen rep.YugoslaviaZambiaZimbabwe
Post Code
CART
Place your promotion here
You have no items in your shopping cart.
( 0 )
home » privacy policy
no results found
more
Privacy Policy
Protecting your privacy is important to Island Style Designs. I make sure that I keep your personal information confidential.  To that end I use a secure gateway - eMatters.
Your personal information is collected strictly for processing your orders only. I may retain your personal information for accounting records. The information is only what you give me upon purchasing one of my products.
Island Style Designs will not ever sell or trade your personal information to anyone. It will not be disclosed to any third party without your prior consent.
Jewellery
Shell, Timber & Bead Jewellery
Silver and Pearl Jewellery
Silver Jewellery
Silver, Shell/Gem Jewellery
Woven Jewellery
Retro Surf
Bits n Pieces
surprise!!!!
